When adding the working memory module registers, it is prudent 
to also bind these controls to the application settings, 
these settings will be loaded next time the program is loaded.
the working memory is used to hold information that may be needed by scripts,
Yet they can be thought of as current information. 
ie: time / Date, Favorites (Color,Car,football team), team results
these are just some of the things we keep in our working memory..
creating memory registers, 
Code will also need to be associated 
with the reigsters for quick retreival of information when requested,
such as "What is the Time?" returning the time, or the date or day etc.., what is your name?, Who made you?
these registers also give a more realistic quality to the bot.
it could be said that these could be used to hold customizable personality traits 
these will need to be edited in a personality editor.